WORK HISTORY

Freelance Designer and Developer

2017 - Present

- Worked with sales planners at Unity Technologies to ideate and design augmented reality advertising mocks for client pitches.
- Designed and developed mobile advertising campaigns for brands including LEGO and Mattel using Javascript, HTML, and CSS.

Web Accessibility Assistant

NYU ITP Accessibility Corp 2018 -2019

- Manually audited site content for Spring 2019 semester classes to ensure compliance with WCAG 2.0/2.1 standards of Web Accessibility using tools such as VoiceOver and keyboard
- Audited content for ITP Camp site against WCAG 2.0/2.1 standards of Web Accessibility using VoiceOver and Keyboard
- Ensured that Issue No.5 of Adjacent, an online journal published by ITP, followed WCAG 2.0/2.1 standards of Web Accessibility using VoiceOver and Keyboard
- Logged accessibility issues uncovered by audits for developers on Github's issue tracker along with suggested solutions to resolve said issues
- Consulted ITP teaching staff on web accessibility tools such as VoiceOver, JAWS, and NVDA and WCAG 2.0/2.1 standards and best practices to ensure future course site content compliance with WCAG 2.0/2.1 Web Accessibility standards

Summer Immersion Program Instructor

Girls Who Code, 2018

- Taught 20 high school students 5 different programming languages over the course of an intensive 7-week program.
- Monitored students' progress and provided guidance and insights on their projects.
- Delegated assignments and tasks to my teaching staff and coordinated classroom logistics.

Interactive Designer

Opera Mediaworks, 2014 - 2016

- Ideated, designed, and developed advertising campaigns that leveraged cutting edge mobile technology to help connect brands with their consumers.
- Consulted members of sales, account management, and operations on the most recent advances in mobile technology and design to accommodate each clients' unique desires and needs.
- Worked with individuals across agencies and teams to make each campaign a success.
- Created mock-ups for colleagues and clients, while also making edits and providing thoughtful solutions to challenges that would materialize through multiple rounds of approval.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

New York University

Interactive Telecommunications MPS, 2019

Parsons School of Design

Communication Design BFA, 2013



CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIST

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a creative technologist and recent graduate of NYU's Interactive Telecommunications Program. Formerly, I was a hybrid interactive designer and developer. In total, I have six years experience using technology and art to create innovative and captivating new experiences. I am driven, resourceful, and have a passion for people.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Javascript | HTML | CSS | PHP | Java | Swift
Python | Arduino C | Git | Wordpress | Node.js
MongoDB | Express | Firebase | Jquery
Photoshop | After Effects | Illustrator
Premiere | Audition | Isadora | Maya | Blender
Vectorworks | Eagle | Fabrication | Electronic
Prototyping | Physical computing | Circuit design
| Machine learning | AR

GET IN TOUCH

Mobile: 908-652-1111 Email: azaleavaseghi@gmail.com Portfolio: www.azaleavaseghi.com LinkedIn: @azaleavaseghi